J
and please stand up.  Don't be
shy here.  Yes.
And your assistant.  Yes,
there.  They have a special
website called the knowledge base.  They
put 5000 videos on there, and we
have another 5000.  They are
preparing 10,000
videos for free and they are working really
hard to do this and they are
also helping with
Lamri and I think they have completed five
courses
, six
courses and then always come back to the
original language.
She and her
assistant, so these 14 years of
Lamrim, you can watch these, you can watch the 14
years
for free.  Let's
give that another round of applause.
Always the same answer.  Once a
year or every 10
years you need some money and
they say no.  These are the only ones who
say no.  No, we don't need it.  It
's okay.
So they accept
donations.  So if
you're looking at the classes on this page
,
then I encourage you
to give them some donations.  The
only people who don't ask me for
money
.  So, you should help them.
I invited her to dinner.